I move differently. I think differently. My belief and my ability cannot be shaken. None of these guys have what I have.
You know my name, yeah? I'm gonna make you tell my name. I am going to break you.
You're gonna be slow. You're gonna be slow. I love it.
To me, it's a great procession.
Every federal agent I'm coming for. Tomorrow I'll take his head clean off.
I am the more content on burning the stream.
How many times can I ask you?
How many days can I go without you?
When I hear you to take part, when I hear you to take over.
People are always saying about the talk, and I talk, and I talk, and I talk.
But guess what? I back it up. I back it up.
While Items
Might be fast.
I have no idea of how to get through.
It's the most embarrassing process.
Decides ask you to read.
The custom blocks you can do.
this is the beginning of the mcgregor era i don't give up i don't give a
i own this town i own rio de janeiro i'm sitting up here with my feet on the desk
what's anyone up there gonna do about it
the fire in my eyes
i don't mind
no
We'll be right back.